<resources>

    <!-- Strings related to About -->


    <!-- about -->
    <string name="about_general_title">GENERAL</string>
    <string name="about_general_summary">FAQr is the ultimate FAQs reader application for Android. You just search for a FAQ by game title, and the FAQ will be downloaded and available for you offline whenever you need it in an easy to use FAQr reader format.</string>
    <string name="about_features_title">FEATURES</string>
    <string name="about_features_summary">
        It used to be that reading ASCII based FAQs on a mobile or tablet device could be a pain.\n
        Finally we have the right tool for the job!\n\n
        \u2605 FAQr always keeps track of your current position in the FAQ so that when you come back to the FAQ you are ready to pick up right back where you left off.\n\n
        \u2605 You can bookmark locations in the FAQ just by long pressing on that section, then you may quickly return it with the My FAQmarks option.\n\n
        \u2605 FAQr automatically configures your reader\'s font sizes and screen configuration, and then every FAQ will automatically load with those settings so that you never need to fool with resizing text again!\n\n
        \u2605 FAQr gives you fast scrolling to quickly access any part of the FAQ in an instant with high precision, and gives you the ability to customize the theme so you can read it how you want to.\n\n
        \u2605 FAQr saves the FAQ for convienent offline reading no matter where you are.\n
    </string>
    <string name="about_disclaimer_title">DISCLAIMER</string>
    <string name="about_disclaimer_summary">
        FAQr is not affiliated with GameFAQs.com in any way.\n\n
        FAQr has been tested on a large number of FAQs, but it hasn\'t been tested on every FAQ. Feel free to use the contact info in Google Play store to report about FAQs that are having problems before simply leaving a poor review.</string>
    <string name="about_more_title">MORE INFO</string>
    <string name="about_more_summary">
        \u2605 Featuring the Final Fantasy IV FAQ by Johnathan \'Zy\' Sawyer\n\n
        \u2605 Using StickyListHeaders developed by Emil Sjölander\n\n
        \u2605 Uses Jsoup HTML Parser by Jonathan Hedley</string>
    <string name="about_donate_title">DONATE</string>
    <string name="about_donate_summary">http://www.faqrapp.com</string>
    <string name="about_contact_title">CONTACT</string>
    <string name="about_contact_summary">Have questions or want to suggest new app features? Please contact faqr.app@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="about_app_title">APP INFO</string>
    <string name="about_version_title">Version</string>
    <string name="about_version_summary">X.X.X</string>

</resources>